(upbeat lively music)
(Sting laughing)
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
♪ Those days are over ♪
♪ You don't have to sell
your body to the night ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ You don't have to wear
that dress tonight ♪
♪ Walk the streets for money ♪
♪ You don't care if it's
wrong or if it's right ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
♪ Put on the red light ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ Ro ♪
(upbeat lively music continues)
♪ I loved you since I knew you ♪
♪ I wouldn't talk down to you ♪
♪ I have to tell you just how I feel ♪
♪ I won't share you with another boy ♪
♪ I know my mind is made up ♪
♪ So put away your makeup ♪
♪ Told you once, I won't tell you again ♪
♪ It's a bad way ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
♪ You don't have ♪
♪ To put on the red light ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ Put on the red light ♪
♪ You don't have ♪
♪ To put on the red light ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ Put on the red light ♪
♪ You don't have ♪
♪ To put on the red light ♪
♪ Roxanne ♪
♪ Put on the red light ♪